[{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":23248,"timeElapsed":146386},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10951,"timeElapsed":157340},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664140595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7432,"timeElapsed":164774},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":10056,"timeElapsed":174832},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664154792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4137,"timeElapsed":178971},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664179449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":24655,"timeElapsed":203628},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664191308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11856,"timeElapsed":215487},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":10897,"timeElapsed":226386},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4869,"timeElapsed":231257},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":20980,"timeElapsed":254999},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5113,"timeElapsed":260114},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5802,"timeElapsed":265918},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3583,"timeElapsed":269502},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664249636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":273815},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664256762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7123,"timeElapsed":280941},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664260722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3958,"timeElapsed":284901},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":288196},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4625,"timeElapsed":292823},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11799,"timeElapsed":306061},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299361,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17477,"timeElapsed":323540},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5923,"timeElapsed":329466},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2978,"timeElapsed":332447},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664310947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2677,"timeElapsed":335125},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664314147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":338326},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":5103,"timeElapsed":343431},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5087,"timeElapsed":348521},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":352033},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3374,"timeElapsed":355409},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":10202,"timeElapsed":367133},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664348363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5407,"timeElapsed":372541},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4977,"timeElapsed":377521},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664361834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8489,"timeElapsed":386013},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3537,"timeElapsed":389552},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5444,"timeElapsed":394998},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2730,"timeElapsed":397729},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6207,"timeElapsed":403938},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2903,"timeElapsed":406843},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14817,"timeElapsed":423466},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4457,"timeElapsed":427925},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6015,"timeElapsed":433941},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":436462},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3088,"timeElapsed":439551},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4242,"timeElapsed":443796},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":446557},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3754,"timeElapsed":450313},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2718,"timeElapsed":453032},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12989,"timeElapsed":467733},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664447063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3507,"timeElapsed":471242},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664457996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10931,"timeElapsed":482174},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664461025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3027,"timeElapsed":485204},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5662,"timeElapsed":490868},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4149,"timeElapsed":495018},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3612,"timeElapsed":498632},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664477728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3272,"timeElapsed":501907},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2985,"timeElapsed":504894},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664505534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":22962,"timeElapsed":529713},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664509842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4306,"timeElapsed":534021},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3985,"timeElapsed":538008},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664517042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3211,"timeElapsed":541221},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664526618,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9574,"timeElapsed":550797},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":555116},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664534673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3735,"timeElapsed":558852},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3412,"timeElapsed":562266},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664541055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2966,"timeElapsed":565234},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664543674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2617,"timeElapsed":567853},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664567354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":22201,"timeElapsed":591533},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3633,"timeElapsed":595168},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664586073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":15081,"timeElapsed":610252},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664589534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3459,"timeElapsed":613712},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664592644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3109,"timeElapsed":616823},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664595575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2929,"timeElapsed":619754},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664598122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2546,"timeElapsed":622301},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664601303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3178,"timeElapsed":625482},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664604333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3028,"timeElapsed":628512},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664624869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":18101,"timeElapsed":649048},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4402,"timeElapsed":653452},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664643064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":13789,"timeElapsed":667243},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664645495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2429,"timeElapsed":669674},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664648683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3185,"timeElapsed":672862},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664653495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4810,"timeElapsed":677674},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664657228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3731,"timeElapsed":681407},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664666036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8805,"timeElapsed":690215},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664669539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3501,"timeElapsed":693718},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664683580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":12116,"timeElapsed":707759},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664686371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2789,"timeElapsed":710550},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664690870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4498,"timeElapsed":715049},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664694218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3346,"timeElapsed":718397},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664697461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3241,"timeElapsed":721640},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664703728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6264,"timeElapsed":727906},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664706967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3238,"timeElapsed":731146},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664716503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":9535,"timeElapsed":740682},{"subjectID":"urbzjy10v3","prolificID":"67532d12a1f7169d484c4fb1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742150b28366d7f2cee5d6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664721500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4994,"timeElapsed":745679}]